blinq.com 2019-04-21

# Privacy Policy - BLINQ

## BLINQ.com PRIVACY POLICY

Welcome to the BLINQ.com Site and Services operated by Optoro, Inc. (“Optoro” “BLINQ.com” “BLINQ®” “we” or “us”). We are committed to respecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes how we collect, use, disclose, store, and otherwise process information when you use our websites and other online products and services. 

**Consent**

By visiting our website or using any of our services, you consent to Optoro’s collection, use, disclosure, transfer, and storage of information relating to you as set forth in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to our practices, please do not subscribe, create an account, make a purchase, or otherwise interact with our services, Optoro’s websites (including BLINQ.com), or our mobile-device applications. 

**Information we collect**

Optoro may collect the following information from you:

**Information you give us**

Optoro collects and stores information you provide through BLINQ.com. This information includes personal information like your name, mailing address, email address, and phone number, and your interests and preferences. If you register, we also collect your username and a password you create and any additional information you provide. Additionally, in certain situations, we may also collect things like your IMEI/UDID (a numeric identifier for your mobile device) or your MAC Address (another kind of numeric identifier for your mobile device), and your credit or debit card information, collectively “Personal Information.” 

**Information you give us about others**

You may give us information about other people, such as the name and email address of another Site visitor. We will only use this information for the specific reason you have provided it.

**Information from other sources**

We may receive information about you from other sources, including third parties that help us update, expand, and analyze our records and identify new users, and provide products and services that may be of interest to you.

**Information collected on our behalf**

We have certain vendors who may collect and process your information on our behalf, such as a credit card processing vendor. When you authorize payment to BLINQ.com, that vendor is accessing your information on our behalf. A vendor who collects reviews will have access to your email address and the products you purchased. We and our vendors may also collect aggregated demographic information.

**Information collected automatically online**

To better serve your needs, we collect information about your interactions with the BLINQ site, including the type of device or browser you’re using, your IP address, your browsing behavior while on our website, and the URLs of the websites you were at before you visited BLINQ.com (these are called “referring URLs”).

Optoro uses technologies such as cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, track users’ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level.

We may permit third party service providers to collect and process some information from BLINQ.com. We may share your personal information with those providers, but they may only use it as needed to perform their functions. Specifically, we may use third-party advertising companies to collect data and/or serve ads when you visit our Web site and thereafter and we may use third-party vendors to test and ensure the security of our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you and to monitor traffic on our website. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, visit  [http://networkadvertising.org/. ](http://networkadvertising.org/)

**Reviews and other content you provide**

Reviews you provide are displayed to assist other shoppers, and may be retained and displayed indefinitely along with your public username.

**How we use the information we collect**

Optoro uses your personal information to provide you products and services, such as to fulfill your requests for products or to help us personalize our offerings to you. We also use your personal information to support our business functions, such as fraud prevention, marketing, and legal functions. To do this, we combine personal and non-personal information, collected online and offline, including information from third party sources. We also use your information to follow up on your purchases and seek feedback and reviews on products. 

**Information retention**

We may retain your information for as long as reasonably necessary to provide you services, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. We may also retain cached or archived copies of your information for a reasonable period of time.

Optoro does not sell, rent, or trade your personal information to third parties. We may share your personal information, such as your email address, to a supplier or vendor who is assisting us in providing services to you. We may combine or share information among current or future Optoro companies, including affiliates and subsidiaries.

Sometimes, we may be required to share personal information for legal reasons, for example, if we are required to do so by a regulation, court order, subpoena, or other legal process. We may also share information when we believe it is necessary to comply with the law or to respond to a government request, or when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect Optoro, our customers, our vendors or others.

We may share personal information in the event of a corporate sale, merger, acquisition, dissolution, or similar event. If such an event takes place, we will notify you through e-mail (if we have your email address) and/or a prominent notice on our applicable website(s) of any change in ownership, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

**How we protect your information**

Security of all information is of the utmost importance for Optoro. Optoro uses technical and physical safeguards to protect the security of your personal information from unauthorized disclosure.

We use a variety of information security measures to protect your online transactions with us.

  * We use reasonable security measures to protect the confidentiality of personal information under our control and appropriately limit access to it, and we ask that our vendors do the same.
  * We use industry-standard SSL (secure socket layer) technology to encrypt and keep your personal and financial data safe when it is transmitted during the checkout process.
  * We hash passwords, and never store them in plain text.

We also make all attempts to ensure that only necessary people and third parties have access to Personal Information.

If you create a username and password, you are responsible for logging out or closing any sessions you open. Do not share your username and password with any other person.

**Your choices / opt-out**

We communicate with users who subscribe to or use our services on a regular basis via email, and we may also communicate by phone or text to resolve customer complaints or investigate suspicious transactions. We may use your email address to confirm your order, notify you of shipment, ask for your feedback on our services and ask you to rate the products received. Generally, users cannot opt out of these communications, which are not marketing related but merely required to complete your transaction with BLINQ.com. 

With regard to marketing related types of communication (promotional emails, direct mail, and mobile marketing communications), Optoro will (i) where legally required only provide you with such information after you have granted your opt-in and (ii) provide you the opportunity to exercise an opt-out choice if you do not want to receive further marketing related types of communication from us. The opt-out choice may be exercised by electing to unsubscribe at the bottom of any marketing communication or by emailing [care@blinq.com. ](mailto:care@blinq.com)If you prefer to have your account removed permanently, please email your request to [care@blinq.com. ](mailto:care@blinq.com)

Please note: Even if we are able to anonymize or make your content or information no longer visible, this does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of your content or personal information from the Internet.

**Protecting children’s privacy**

We are committed to protecting children’s privacy on the internet and we do not make our website available to minors under the age of eighteen (18) and do not knowingly collect personal information from children under that age.

**Links to other websites**

BLINQ.com links to other websites, many of which have their own privacy policies. Be sure to review the privacy policy on the website you are visiting.

**Social media features**

BLINQ.com includes ways to interact and share using social media, through features such as the Facebook “Like” button, or the “Share This” button. These features may collect information such as your IP address or the page you are visiting on our website, and may set cookies to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features can be hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our website. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the social media company providing the feature. 

**Privacy Policy updates**

We may need to update our Privacy Policy as we and our users grow and evolve. If we make material changes, we will notify you by e-mail (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of posting a notice on this website thirty (30) days prior to the change becoming effective, as well as inform you of any choices you may have with respect to these changes.

**Your California rights**

CEM: California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits users of our website that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email [care@blinq.com ](mailto:care@blinq.com)or write us at 1001 G Street, NW, Suite 1200, Washington, DC 20001 ATTN: General Counsel. 

**International Users – Consent to Transfer and Processing**

The Service is hosted in the United States. If you are visiting the Service from outside the United States, your information may be transferred to, stored and processed in the United States in accordance with this Privacy Policy and applicable United States laws. The United States laws with respect to data protection and privacy may not be as comprehensive as those laws or regulations in your country or may otherwise differ from the data protection or consumer protection laws in your country. By using the Service, you consent to transfer of your information to our facilities as described in this Privacy Policy. 

**CONTACT US**

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy or practices, please contact us.

Phone: 301-760-7003  
E-mail: [care@blinq.com ](mailto:care@blinq.com)  
Address:  
Optoro (Attn: General Counsel)  
1001 G St. NW Suite 1200  
Washington, DC 20001 

Last Updated: December 18, 2017 © Optoro, Inc.
